CENTER FOR COMMUNITY STUDIES RECORDS (UA652) 1825-1976
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Activities and Programs, 1825-1976; 2; 12
  - Council of Jewish Women, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - The Council of Educational Needs, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Counselor Personality, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Courses 1938, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Courses, 1947-1957 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Courses, 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Courses, 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Courses, 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Courses, 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Courses, 1951-1966 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Courses, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Courses, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Courses, 1956-1957; Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Courses, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Courses, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Courses, 1959-1961 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Courses, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Courses, 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Courses, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Courses, 1964-1967 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Courses, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Courses, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Courses, 1966-1971 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Courses, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Courses, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Courses, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Courses, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Courses, Sociology Problems, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Student, Paper, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Student, Education Philosophy 601, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Cummings, E.E., The Cambridge Ladies, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Curriculum Conference, 1963 February 12 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Davis, Herbert, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Davis, John A., “Negro Employment: a Process Report,” Fortune, July, 1952 July (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Day, E.D., Education for Freedom and Responsibility, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Definition of the Field of Community Studies, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Department of Education, 1936-1946 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - A Descriptive Analysis of Amsterdam, New York, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - A Descriptive Analysis of Amsterdam, New York (Folder 2), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Developments in Education in the 1960s, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Disney, M., M. Reiss, and B. Sherman, "The Community-Centered School,", 1952 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Dissertation Abstracts, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Dissertation for the Years, 1959-1963 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Dissertation Requirements, and Procedures, in Educational Administration, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Doctoral Dissertation Committee, Student, 1960-1965 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Doctors of Education Program, 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Doctoral Program, 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Donley, D.T., The Administrator and Communication, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Student, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Student, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - East Greenbush Adult Education Department, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - East Greenbush School Registration, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Eastern New York Regional TEPS Conference, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Education Department Committee Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Education 20 Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Education-Industry Cooperation, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Education Programs, Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Education Questions and Statements, Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Educational Administrative, 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Educational Administrative, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Educational Administrative, 1962-1966 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Educational Alliance, 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Student, Transfer of Training, Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Ethnics and Issues Facing Teachers, 1952-1954 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Evaluation of Wallingford Schools, Connecticut State Department of Education, Undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - The Exploratory Group for the Center for Community Studies, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - The Exploratory Group for the Center for Community Studies, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Questionnaire Analyses, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Studnet, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - The Ford Foundation Teacher Education Proposal to Arkansas, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Foundation of Education Department, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Student, Culture and Personality the Psychosocial Approach to a Democratic Social Order, Undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Student, Educational Leadership and Administrative Competencies, Undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Fredonia Project, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Student, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Fundraising Information, Undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Student, Undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Geneseo Project, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Student, Soc. 408, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Get out the Vote Campaign, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Gloversville Workshop, 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Student, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Guide for Students: Handbook of Procedures Followed in the Programs of Advanced Studies in Educational Administration, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Guide for Students: Handbook of Procedures Followed in the Programs of Advanced Studies in Educational Administration, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Hadlock, R., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Harpur College, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Healthcare and Hospitals, Photographs, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Health and Dental Hygiene, Photographs, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - High School Diplomas in New York State, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Hillz Knowlton Resources Directory, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Hillsdale Center, Future Plans, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Historical Materials, 1910-1922 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - History of Education Society, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Holliday, Al, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - . Humanities Seminar for School Administrators: Loyalty, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Huntington, Edward F, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Individual, Community and Symbolism, Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Industrial and Labor Relations Conference at Cornell, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Inglis, Robert D., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Institute of Applied Arts and Sciences at New York City, Brooklyn Institute, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Institute on Community Leadership, 9th Annual, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Intergroup Studies Projects, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Interim Report of the Director Center for Community Studies, New York State College for Teachers, 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Intermountain Indian School, Utah, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Interracial Council, Albany, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Is My Educational Philosophy Conservative or Progressive?, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Student, Building Better Relations with Business, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Jackman, William M., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Jeffers, Verne, "Projecting Pupulation Trends in a School District,", 1961 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Jewish Community Center, 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Junior Red Cross, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Keir, Charles W., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Kelley, Robert, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Kenwood Mills Project, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Kimball, Kenneth R., 1961 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Kingston Public Schools Second Mid-year Conference, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Kohn, Elizabeth Bell, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Lake Placid Conference, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Language Center Project, Undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Lansingburg Conference, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Student, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Student, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Leaders Conferences, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Leadership Training Conference, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Leigh, Edward, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Leonard, Gregory, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Liaison Group to Programs of Advanced Studies in Educational Administration, Undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Student, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Log Education 317, 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Log Sociology 110, 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Logs, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Student, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Student, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Student, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Student, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Student, Undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Student, "Sydney Smith: A Study of His Writings on Education,", Undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Student, "Sydney Smith: A Study of His Writings on Education,", Undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Student, Notebook, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Student, Undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Memoranda, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Middle Atlantic States Philosophy of Education Conference, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Student, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Student, Research Project, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Moral Aspects of Education, Undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Moral Education, Undated (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Student, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Musella, Donald, "Open-Closedmindedness as a Factor in the Rating of Teachers by Administrators,", 1964 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - The National Conference of Christian and Jews, 1950-1953 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - National Conference of Professors of Educational Administration, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - National Council for the Social Studies, Undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - National School Public Relations Association, Undated (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - The Nature and Sources of Educational Objectives, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - NDEA, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Neighborhood Studies, 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - New Berlin Central School Project, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - New Paltz Action Research, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - News Clippings, 1949-1953 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - New York State Association of Councils and Chests, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - New York State Citizen’s Councils, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Niles, Paula, " Philosophy of Education,", 1976 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Notes, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Notes, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Notes, Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Notes, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Notes, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Notes, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Notes, Americanization, Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Notes, Americanization, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Notes, Americanization, Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Notes, Americanization, Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Notes, East Side of New York, Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Notes, Educational History, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Notes, Educational History, Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Notes, Honors Programs, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Notes, Immigrants, Undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Notes, Immigrants, Undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Notes, Social Aspects of Education, Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Off Campus Student Teaching, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Student, Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Papers, Islam, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Partial Bibliography for “Community, Society, and the Schools,”, Undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Philip Livingston Project, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Phinney, J.T., 1964 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Photosgraphs, Undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - PICT, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Student, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Plan for Research and Writing Project to Take Place during the Six-Week Summer Session, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Plattsburgh State Teachers College, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Pollak, Peter, The Intercollegiate Socialist Society, Student, Undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Poliomylitis Vaccine Project, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Poliomylitis Vaccine Project, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Poliomylitis Vaccine Project, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Poliomylitis Vaccine Project, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Poliomylitis Vaccine Project, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Potsdam State Teachers College, Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Preliminary Report of the Committee Appointed by the Council of Community Services, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Preliminary Report on the TV Course Geography 4, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Present Status and Future Plans for the Center for Community Studies, 1951-1953 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - President’s Conference at Fredonia, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Principalship Specialization, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Programs of Advanced Studies in Educational Administration, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Proposal of a Cooperative Research Foundation of the State University of New York, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Progress Report of the Center for Community Studies, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Proposal for a Conference on Community Studies and Intergroup Relations, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Public Opinion Study, 1925-1978 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Public Relations, Photographs, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Public Services of the Units of the State University, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Publicity, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - A Proposed Project to Improve Instruction in the Early College Years, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Recreational Needs of the Arbor Hill Clinton Square Area, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Regents in New York State, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Religious Study, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Report of Amsterdam Meeting, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Report Casework Committee, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Report of the Conference of Representatives of the New York State Teachers College on Grants-in-Aid, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Report of the Graduate Council, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Report of the Meeting of the State University Committee on Community Studies, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Report of the Planning Conference on Community and Intergroup Relations in Teachers Education, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Report on the Conduct and Utilization of TV Geography 4, Undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Report on Cortland Conference, Original Notes and Copies, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Report on Doctoral Colloquium, 1963 January 17 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Report on the Present Status of the Center for Community Studies and Recommendations, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Report on Proposed Graduate Programs in History and Philosophy of Education, Undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Report on the Task Force of Institution, Undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Revised Rating Scale for Advanced Program Students, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Student, Dissertation Proposal, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Student, Philosophy of Education 601, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Saint Adalbert’s School, Undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Saint John the Evangelist School, Undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Saint Luke's School, Undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Saint Luke's School, Undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Saint Mary's School, Undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Student, Education 317, Student Report, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Student, Student Project, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - San Jose Program, Developing the Content of the, Chapter 5, Undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Schedule for Analysis of Community Action Programs, Undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Schedules, 1958-1976 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Scheible, Mary, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - The School Administrator and Public Problems in the 60s, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - School of Education Curriculum Committee, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - School Public Relations, 1948-1951 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - School Taxations, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Schools and Institutions, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Second Annual First Year Teacher’s Clink, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Second Cortland Conference, 1952 June (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Second Eastern College Conference on Functional Education, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Secondary School Curriculum in New York State, 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Service Organizations Report, Albany, 1951-1956 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Services to Art and Culture, Photographs, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Services to Farmers, Photographs, 1953-1955 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Services to Forestry, Photographs, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Services to the Home, Photographs, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Services to Industry, Photographs, Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Services to Schools, Photographs, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Services to Television and Radio, Photographs, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Setauket Project, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Sherman, Arnold, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Student, Dissertation Proposal, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Student, Education 201, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Smith, C.Curien, New Wine in Old Bottles, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Student, Student Project, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Social Problems and Change, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Social Services in Schools, 1957-1964 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Some Observations and Suggestions by Alfred J. Cali, Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Sovereignty, Situations, and Security, Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Sovereignty, Situations, and Security, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Special Projects, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Speech Therapy Clinic, Photographs, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Standing, T.G., 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Standing, T.G., The Problems of Consensus in the Modern Community, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - State Carities Aid Associations, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - State University College for Teachers at Buffalo, Undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - State University, Rensselaerville Institute Programs, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - A Statistical Study of the Wallingford School System, 1946 September (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Structural and Functional Change for Cooperation as an Aspect of Complex Organization Adaptation, Undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Student and Academic Conference, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Student Community Job Assignments, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Student Details, Undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Student Details, Undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Student Interviews, Undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Student Opinion Panel, Undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Student Opinion Panel, Undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Student Participation in College and Community Activities, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Student Participation in College and Community Activities, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Student Questionnaires, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Student Questionnaires, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Student Questionnaires, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Student Questionnaires, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Student Questionnaires, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Student Questionnaires, Undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - “A Study of the Community Aspirations of Amsterdam, New York,”, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Study of Opinion on Medicine and Child Health, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Study of Opinion on Medicine and Child Health, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Study of Opinion on Medicine and Child Health, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Supplementary Information on Assistantships and Fellowships, Undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Surveys, Students, 1954-1961 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Swimming Surveys, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Swire, Leslie, Educational Philosophy, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Syracuse University Students Development Test, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Teacher In-service Education Inventory, Undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Teaching Internship, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Temporary Shelter and Detention Care of Children in Albany and Rensselaer Counties, 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Term Papers, Students, 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Testing Materials, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Third Annual Curriculum Conference for School Administrators: The Disaffected Child, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Student, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Trends in High School Subjects, 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Twenty-Second Annual Meeting of the Society for Applied Anthropology, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Student, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - The University Certificate, Undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - University Community Cooperation Project, 1949-1953 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - University Community Cooperation Project, 1950/1955 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - University Community Cooperation Project, 1950/1955 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - The University of the State of New York, Education Department, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Van Cleve, Donald, 1951-1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Van Cleve, Donald, 1954-1975 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Van Cleve, Donald, 1960-1962 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Van Cleve, Donald, 1962-1965 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Van Cleve, Donald, 1965-1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Van Corlaer School, Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Vaughn, Harold A. Jr., 1951 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Vassar Summer Institute “What Can Communities Do?”, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Student, Educational Philosophy 601, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - What is the Nature of the Problem Facing our Communities, Undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Wick, Rollo E., Correspondence, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Student, Dissertation Proposal, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Woodlawn School, Undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Woodlawn School, Undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Workshop Plans, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Workshops, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Workshops, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Wynne, John P., Philosophies of Educations, Undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Yates School, Undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Yates School, Undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Student, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Zoller School, Undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Zoller School, Undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Courses, 1951-1953 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Census Classification Project, 1825-1890 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Students, The Community Centered School, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Geneseo-Cortland Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - High School Student Logs, 1937-1939 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Illich, Ivan, Why We Must Abolish Schooling, Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - The Immigrant and the Public School, Undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - The Immigrant and the Public School, Undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - The Immigrant and the Public School, Undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - New York College for Teachers Student Participation Study, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Projective Devices, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Public Opinion Polls, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Research, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Student Questionnaires, 1935-1938 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Student Questionnaires, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Student Questionnaires, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Student Questionnaires, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Student Questionnaires, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Student Questionnaires, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 22)